permanent: adj. 永久的
Lesson 52. Mud is mud. My cousin, Harry, keeps a large curiously shaped bottle on permanent
第52课。泥是泥。我的堂兄哈利（Harry）在永久的
tint: v.   给……染色, delicate: adj. 淡色的, shade: n.   色度
display in his study. Despite the fact that the bottle is tinted a delicate shade of green,
在他的书房中展示。尽管该瓶子被染成绿色的细微阴影，但
observant: adj. 观察力敏锐的
an observant visitor would soon notice that it is filled with what looks like a thick.
一个观察的访客很快会注意到它充满了看起来像厚的东西。
Grays substance. If you were to ask Harry what was in the bottle, he would tell you that it
灰色物质。如果你问哈利，瓶子里有什么，他会告诉你
contained perfumed mud. If you expressed doubt or surprise, he would immediately invite you to
含有香料的泥浆。如果您表示怀疑或惊讶，他会立即邀请您
dispel: v.   驱散，消除
smell it and then to rub some into your skin. This brief experiment would dispel any further
闻到它，然后将一些摩擦到您的皮肤中。这个简短的实验将进一步驱散
doubts you might have. The bottle really does contain perfumed mud. How Harry came into the
您可能会怀疑。该瓶确实确实含有香水的泥浆。哈利如何进入
outlandish: adj. 稀奇古怪的
possession of this outlandish stuff makes an interesting story which he is. Fond of relating,
拥有这种古怪的东西使他成为一个有趣的故事。喜欢联系，
acquisition: n.   获得
furthermore, the acquisition of this bottle cured him of a bad habit he had been developing for
此外，收购这个瓶子使他养成了他一直在养成的坏习惯
cosmetic: n.   化妆品
years. Harry used to consider it a great joke to go into expensive cosmetic shops and make out
年。哈利曾经认为这是一个开玩笑的开玩笑，然后去昂贵的化妆品商店
fanciful: adj. 想像出来的
rages. Requests for goods that do not exist he would invent fanciful names on the spot.
愤怒。对不存在的商品的要求，他将当场发明奇特的名字。
insoluble: adj. 不可溶解的
On entering a shop, he would ask for a new perfume called scented shadow or for insoluble bath
在进入商店时，他会要求一种新的香水，称为气味阴影或不溶性浴室
cubes. If a shop assistant told him she had not heard of it, he would pretend to be considerably
立方体。如果商店助手告诉他她没有听说过，他会假装很大
put out. He loved to be told that one of his imaginary products was temporarily out of stock and
推出。他喜欢被告知他的一种虚构产品暂时缺货，
he would. Faithfully promised to call again at some future date, but of course he never did.
他会。忠实地答应在以后的某个日期再次打电话，但他当然从未这样做。
How Harry managed to keep a straight face during these performances is quite beyond me.
哈利在这些表演中如何设法保持直面的面孔超出了我的范围。
prompt: v.   敦促，激励
Harry does not need to be prompted to explain how he bought his precious bottle of mud.
不需要提示哈利（Harry）来解释他如何购买他珍贵的泥浆。
exclusive: adj. 专售高档商品的
One day, he went to an exclusive shop in London and asked for, Myrolite.
有一天，他去了伦敦的一家独家商店，并要求肉饼。
syllable: n.   音节
The shop assistant looked puzzled and Harry repeated the word, slowly stressing each syllable.
商店助理看上去很困惑，哈利重复了这个词，慢慢地强调了每个音节。
bewilderment: n.   迷惑，糊涂
When the woman shook her head in bewilderment, Harry went on to explain that Myrolite was a hard.
当那个女人迷惑地摇了摇头时，哈利继续解释说肉豆蔻是很难的。
freckle: n.   雀斑, evidently: adv. 显然的，明显地
Amber liked substance which could be used to remove freckles. This explanation evidently
琥珀色的物质可用于去除雀斑。这显然是这样的解释
weird: adj. 奇异的，古怪的
conveyed something to the woman who searched shelf after shelf. She produced all sorts of weird
向搜寻架子架子的女人传达了一些东西。她产生了各种各样的怪异
concoction: n.   调制品
concoctions, but none of them met with Harry's requirements. When Harry put on his act of being
混合物，但它们都没有达到哈利的要求。当哈利施加了他的行为
mildly annoyed, the assistant promised to order some for him. Intoxicated by his success,
助手很生气，答应为他订购一些。因他的成功而陶醉
blank: adj. 无表情的，茫然的
Harry then asked for perfumed mud. He expected the assistant to look at him in blank astonishment.
哈利然后要求泥泞的泥浆。他希望助手惊讶地看着他。
However, it was his turn to be surprised. For the woman's eyes immediately lit up and she
但是，轮到他感到惊讶了。因为女人的眼睛立即亮了，她
fetched several bottles which she placed on the counter for Harry to inspect. For once,
她放在柜台上供哈利检查了几瓶瓶子。一次，
discreetly: adv. 谨慎地
Harry had to admit defeat. He picked up what seemed to be the smallest bottle and discreetly
哈利不得不承认失败。他捡起了似乎是最小的瓶子，谨慎的
asked the price. He was glad to get away with a mere 20 pounds and he beat a hasty retreat.
问价格。他很高兴能仅仅20磅重20磅，击败了仓促的撤退。
Clutching the precious bottle under his arm. From then on, Harry decided that this little game he
抓住他手臂下的珍贵瓶子。从那时起，哈利决定了他
adorn: v.   装饰，打扮
had invented might prove to be expensive. The curious bottle, which now adorns the bookcase in his
发明的可能被证明是昂贵的。好奇的瓶子，现在装饰着他的书架
cosmetic: n.   化妆品
study, was his first and last purchase of rare cosmetics.
研究是他第一次也是最后一次购买稀有化妆品。